If I recall,
it was uh...
Loser of this game
owes the other
ten million dollars.
And...
Has to leave the
NFL permanently.
Ten million dollars?
I could work
my whole life and
never make
that money.
Ted.
Have mercy, can we?
We used to
be colleagues.
Remember? We...
I don't have
ten million dollars.
And if I'm forced
out of the NFL,
I'll have no job.
You can't let
him off like that!
If it weren't
for him,
we wouldn't have
been sabotaged!
He cost our
guys everything.
He has to pay!
Yeah, guys
like him are poison.
Come on, coach.
You can't let him
get away with this.
Okay.
Ted, I was wrong.
I never should have
done what I did.
And if you
forgive me, I will do
anything you ask.
As per our bet,
you leave the
NFL permanently.
But out of the
kindness of my heart,
I'll drop the ten
million dollars.
But
you need to apologize
to every
single
one of my players.
Yeah.
No, no problem.
Yeah. Come here.
Really sorry
about it. Really.
Really sorry...
Hey, man.
Really sorry about it.
Really
sorry about it.
Really sorry.
You got a great arm,
by the way.
You!
Son of a bitch!
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be forced
out of the NFL.
He told me to take
out your players.
He did.
I'm gonna
tell on him.
I'm gonna report
him to the police.